{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\GianLuigi4.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "mettersi",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1487788440.2387123,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to put on\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "giusto",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487788231.8949132,
            "question": "Given the definition \"corret, fair\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to be hungry",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487788155.263826,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"avere fame\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ridere",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487788210.9793293,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to laugh\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to taste",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1487788442.767014,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"assagiare\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "farsi male",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1487788190.3994222,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to get hurt\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la correzione",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1487788396.4680226,
            "question": "Given the definition \"correction\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "preferito",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487788234.6229782,
            "question": "Given the definition \"favorite\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "repeat"
            ],
            "answer": "to repeat",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487788465.2987394,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ripetere\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "fried chicken",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487788446.0229788,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il pollo fritto\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Anything else?"
            ],
            "answer": "What else?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487788459.1706069,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Che altro?\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to fry",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487788486.442196,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"friggere\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "potato",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487788448.5831437,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la patata\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "bean",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487788480.7533128,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il fagiolo\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "contare",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487788483.9989066,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to sing\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "niente"
            ],
            "answer": "nient",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487788453.2228813,
            "question": "Given the definition \"nothing\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "toccare",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487788575.143725,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to touch\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il carciofo",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1487788655.4672198,
            "question": "Given the definition \"artichoke\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "oil",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487788527.6655023,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"l'olio\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "electric stove"
            ],
            "answer": "stove",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487788495.0059714,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la cucina elettica\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "pea",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487788525.081901,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il pisello\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la pietanza",
            "failed": 10,
            "lastAsked": 1487788660.7149985,
            "question": "Given the definition \"dish or food\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il pisello",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1487788609.2518177,
            "question": "Given the definition \"pea\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sentire",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1487788620.9367113,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to listen\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "correct, fair"
            ],
            "answer": "corret, fair",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1487788784.3124037,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"giusto\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il cavolo",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1487788856.5637465,
            "question": "Given the definition \"cabbage\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "eggplant",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1487788863.923672,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la melanzana\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il forno",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1487788867.1396692,
            "question": "Given the definition \"oven\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il nomignolo",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1487788812.9969945,
            "question": "Given the definition \"nickname\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to get burned",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1487788897.5751762,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"bruciarsi\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la cucina elettica",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1487788894.6629844,
            "question": "Given the definition \"stove\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to put on",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1487788771.857074,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"mettersi\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "girare",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1487789039.9760244,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to stir, turn\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il brano",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1487789043.3682456,
            "question": "Given the definition \"passage\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "brussel sprout",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1487788992.4570315,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il cavolino\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la melanzana",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1487789030.43247,
            "question": "Given the definition \"eggplant\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "il passatempo"
            ],
            "answer": "il passsatempo",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1487788998.9766848,
            "question": "Given the definition \"hobby, passtime\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to suggest",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1487788995.265003,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"suggerire\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "bruciarsi",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1487789003.036955,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to get burned\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to get hurt",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487788926.530243,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"farsi male\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il ravanello",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1487789173.8370192,
            "question": "Given the definition \"radish\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to laugh",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487789062.5401382,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ridere\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to stire or turn"
            ],
            "answer": "to stir, turn",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1487789111.714954,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"girare\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "food or dish"
            ],
            "answer": "dish or food",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1487789107.4025595,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la pietanza\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il cavolino",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1487789180.541565,
            "question": "Given the definition \"brussel sprout\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "assagiare",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487789046.9520757,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to taste\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to sing",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1487789121.0427465,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"contare\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "formaggino"
            ],
            "answer": "il formaggino",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1487789168.0768065,
            "question": "Given the definition \"cheese\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "terzo",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487789183.9615016,
            "question": "Given the definition \"third\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "aspettare",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1487789234.7643733,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to wait (for)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to add",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487789229.9485228,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"aggiungere\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "profumo"
            ],
            "answer": "il profumo",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1487789273.88472,
            "question": "Given the definition \"smell, odor, perfume\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "suggerire",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1487789295.0077846,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to suggest\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "aggiungere",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1487789269.2517953,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to add\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to touch",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487789231.9490285,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"toccare\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "che altro?"
            ],
            "answer": "Che altro?",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1487789280.1002035,
            "question": "Given the definition \"What else?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "fagiolo"
            ],
            "answer": "il fagiolo",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487789405.3974626,
            "question": "Given the definition \"bean\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "decidere",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487789412.4534283,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to decide\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "passage",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487789365.6822896,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il brano\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to wait (for)",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487789298.6952212,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"aspettare\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "sale"
            ],
            "answer": "il sale",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487789314.9474857,
            "question": "Given the definition \"salt\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la carota",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487789402.529764,
            "question": "Given the definition \"carrot\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "decimo",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487789335.1827247,
            "question": "Given the definition \"tenth\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'insalata",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487789388.0783734,
            "question": "Given the definition \"salad\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il pepe",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487789541.7349532,
            "question": "Given the definition \"pepper\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "passtime, hobby"
            ],
            "answer": "hobby, passtime",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487789470.7322717,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il passsatempo\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "i peperoni",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487789571.3227272,
            "question": "Given the definition \"peppers\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "eighth",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487789567.6587188,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ottavo\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "quinto",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487789416.7496064,
            "question": "Given the definition \"fifth\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "seventh",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487789563.6909788,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"settimo\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "cucinare",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487789579.7702513,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to cook\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ripetere",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487789575.154771,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to repeat\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "completare",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487789659.5245788,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to complete\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "nickname",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487789608.1579363,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il nomignolo\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sesto",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1487789661.3967311,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sixth\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ninth",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487789653.524956,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"nono\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "friggere",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487789596.437881,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to fry\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "dodicesimo",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487789650.8693638,
            "question": "Given the definition \"twelveth\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "oven",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487789613.7658293,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il forno\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "prepparare",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487789656.9730682,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to prepare\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il pollo fritto",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487789713.755916,
            "question": "Given the definition \"fried chicken\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "radish",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487789666.977158,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il ravanello\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "quarto",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487789715.9318824,
            "question": "Given the definition \"fourth\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "cabbage",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487789664.2526767,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il cavolo\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "artichoke",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1487789725.279633,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il carciofo\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il contrario",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487789719.1515148,
            "question": "Given the definition \"opposite, antonym\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ottavo",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487789710.411825,
            "question": "Given the definition \"eighth\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il rosmarino",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487789722.1519756,
            "question": "Given the definition \"rosemary (spice)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "undicesimo",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487789731.8637123,
            "question": "Given the definition \"eleventh\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "favorite",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487789744.7199924,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"preferito\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "antonym"
            ],
            "answer": "opposite, antonym",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789736.9276679,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il contrario\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "carrot",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789763.211621,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la carota\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino a",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487789766.4754877,
            "question": "Given the definition \"near\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "il secondo",
                "secondo"
            ],
            "answer": "second",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789752.4919312,
            "question": "Given the definition \"second\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il pomodoro",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789741.1591752,
            "question": "Given the definition \"tomato\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "primo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789760.987733,
            "question": "Given the definition \"first\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "rosemary"
            ],
            "answer": "rosemary (spice)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789774.5596015,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il rosmarino\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "12th"
            ],
            "answer": "twelveth",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789787.5831044,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"dodicesimo\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "pepper",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789790.614415,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il pepe\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "secondo"
            ],
            "answer": "second",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789769.5549946,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"second\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la cipolla",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789782.246437,
            "question": "Given the definition \"onion\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to decide",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789803.7949815,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"decidere\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "perfume, scent",
                "perfume"
            ],
            "answer": "smell, odor, perfume",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789798.8189716,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il profumo\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to complete",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789801.5061588,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"completare\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "tenth",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789834.7502155,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"decimo\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sixth",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789826.4304063,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"sesto\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "pollo"
            ],
            "answer": "il pollo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789807.0256486,
            "question": "Given the definition \"chicken\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "eleventh",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789814.8741963,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"undicesimo\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "third",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789829.1252184,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"terzo\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "correction",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789818.2094007,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la correzione\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "chicken",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789831.9260077,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il pollo\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "salt",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487789836.4053288,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il sale\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "fourth",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789843.8371372,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"quarto\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "tomato",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789838.8625522,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il pomodoro\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to listen",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789856.5536873,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"sentire\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "nono",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789858.288448,
            "question": "Given the definition \"ninth\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "cheese",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789846.49337,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il formaggino\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to prepare",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789841.245358,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"prepparare\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "patata"
            ],
            "answer": "la patata",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487789864.6175709,
            "question": "Given the definition \"potato\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "fifth",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789860.689341,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"quinto\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "onion",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789877.7938392,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la cipolla\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "peppers",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789872.5856407,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"i peperoni\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "avere fame",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789884.8049958,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be hungry\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'estate",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789867.5535626,
            "question": "Given the definition \"summer\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "salad",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789879.8613772,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"l'insalata\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "close"
            ],
            "answer": "near",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789875.200217,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"vicino a\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "first",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789881.6538768,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"primo\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'olio",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789869.5767224,
            "question": "Given the definition \"oil\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "none"
            ],
            "answer": "nothing",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789954.9600966,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"nient\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "settimo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789948.0241456,
            "question": "Given the definition \"seventh\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to cook",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789957.3638985,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"cucinare\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "summer",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487789950.2804573,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"l'estate\"?",
            "tried": 2
        }
    ]
}